gamersheroes.com 2018-11-27

# Privacy Policy - GamersHeroes

## Who we are

Our website address is: http://www.gamersheroes.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

We collect data regarding your browsing history on the website. This allows us to track performance and monitor any potential security problems. We also serve ads based on your browsing history, which can be removed by clearing your cookies in your browser. None of the information we collect can be used to identify you or locate you in any way, shape or form.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

Any data or personal information provided in one of our contact forms will solely be used to deal with that specific inquiry. Your email, personal information or data will not be kept or shared.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

## Who we share your data with

When you browse the website and visit articles, Google Analytics stores the information so we can improve site performance and monitor potential security issues. This information is anonymized prior to our receiving it. This means your IP address and any other identifiable information is not received or stored.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. Please email captaincamper@gamersheroes.com for any data related requests.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Your contact information

Outside of contact forms (see above) we do not request or store any personal contact information on this website

## Additional information

### How we protect your data

We partner with highly reputable services and businesses. WordPress and Google are world known organizations. 

### What data breach procedures we have in place

If a data breach is detected, users will be informed within 72 hours

### What third parties we receive data from

We receive information through our primary advertising partner (http://enthusiastgaming.com/) in relation to advertising interaction. However, none of this information is personal and cannot be used to identify or locate you in any way.

### What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data

We do not.
